Privacy Policy

ARUBA

v.2.6\_ASOn_23.10.2023

1

Aruba S.p.A.

Via San Clemente No.53, Ponte San Pietro 24036 (BG)

VAT Reg. No. 01573850516 | Tax ID No. 04552920482

REA [Administrative and Economic Index] BG 434483 | Share Capital € 4,000,000 fully paid up | Certified email:

aruba@aruba.pec.it | Website aruba.it

Privacy Policy pursuant to Articles 13 and 14 of Regulation (EU) 2016/679

Pursuant to Articles 13 and 14 of Regulation (EU) 2016/679 (the “Regulation”), Aruba S.p.A. (“Aruba” or “Data Controller”), hereby provides

below to its customers, including potential customers, as well as third parties in general (e.g. delegates, legal representatives, etc.) who come

in contact with Aruba on behalf of or as mandated by customers, including potential customers (the “Data Subjects”), the information required

by law relating to the processing of their personal data (“Data”).

ABOUT

US

Data Controller Aruba S.p.A., with registered office in Ponte San Pietro (BG) at Via San Clemente No. 53

privacy@staff.aruba.it

Data Protection Officer (DPO) dpo@staff.aruba.it

HOW WE COLLECT

PERSONAL DATA

The data processed by the Data Controller are acquired as follows:

• from the Data Subject, also through remote communications techniques used by the Data Controller (e.g. websites, smartphone and tablet

apps, call centres, etc.);

• from third parties (e.g. those arranging transactions for the Data Subject, business information etc.).

Data from public sources, such as public registers, lists, public domain documents (e.g. information contained in the register of companies at

the Chambers of Commerce,

WHAT DATA

DO WE PROCESS

CATEGORY OF DATA EXAMPLES OF TYPES OF DATA

Personal information Name, surname, street address, nationality, province and municipality of residence, landline and/or

mobile phone number, , taxpayer ID number, email address, the details of identity document of which

a copy is acquired where applicable .

Banking information IBAN and banking/postal account information (except for Credit Card number).

Log Source IP address, Log (system and network)

Internet traffic Data In case of Mail or Connectivity Services: Data processed for the purpose of the conveyance of a

communication on an electronic communications network or for the billing thereof.

WHY ARE THE DATA SUBJECT'S

DATA NEEDED

PURPOSES OF THE PROCESSING LEGAL BASIS

Registration and management of contact requests and/or

information materials

The Data Subject's personal data are processed to implement

preliminary actions and those following a registration request, to

manage information and contact requests, and/or to send

informational materials, as well as to satisfy any and all other

obligations arising herewith.

The legal basis for this processing is to provide the services relating to a

request for registration, information and contact and/or to send information

materials and to comply with legal requirements.

The provision of the data is optional. However if the Data Subject refuses to

provide the data, it will not be possible for the Data Controller to provide the

requested service.

Management of the contractual relationship

The Data Subject's personal data are processed to implement

actions in preparation of and following the purchase of a Service

and/or a Product, such as management of the relevant order,

provision of the Service itself and/or production and/or shipping

of the purchased Product, related invoicing and payment

management, handling of any claims and/or notifications to the

support service and provision of the support itself, sending

The legal basis for this processing is to provide the services relating to the

pre-contractual and contractual relationship and to comply with the legal

requirements.

The provision of the data is optional. However if the Data Subject refuses to

provide the data, it will not be possible for the Data Controller to provide the

requested service.

Privacy Policy

ARUBA

v.2.6\_ASOn_23.10.2023

2

Aruba S.p.A.

Via San Clemente No.53, Ponte San Pietro 24036 (BG)

VAT Reg. No. 01573850516 | Tax ID No. 04552920482

REA [Administrative and Economic Index] BG 434483 | Share Capital € 4,000,000 fully paid up | Certified email:

aruba@aruba.pec.it | Website aruba.it

communications for information as well as fulfilment of any and

all other obligations arising from the contract.

Defending a right in court or out of court

The Data Subject's personal data are processed to ascertain,

exercise or defend a right of the Data Controller and/or to defend

itself against third party claims, in court or out of court.

The legal basis of the processing is the pursuit of the legitimate interest of

the Data Controller, given the balance of the rights of the latter and the Data

Subject.

Information Security

The Data Subject's personal data are processed to ensure

network and information security, the protection of corporate

assets and corporate systems.

The legal basis for this processing is compliance with the law and the pursuit

of the legitimate interest of the Data Controller, given the balance of rights

of the latter and the Data Subject.

The Data Subject has the right to object at any time to the processing of

their personal data for the purpose in question, on grounds relating to their

personal situation.

Fraud prevention

The Data Subject's personal data are processed to allow

controls that monitor and prevent fraudulent payments by

software systems running automated checks, prior to the

negotiation of Services/Products. If these checks return a

negative result it will be impossible to complete the transaction;

the Data Subject can, of course, express their opinion, request

an explanation, or challenge the decision by sending their

reasons to Customer Support or to privacy@staff.aruba.it.

The legal basis of the processing is the pursuit of the legitimate interest of

the Data Controller, given the balance of the rights of the latter and the Data

Subject.

The Data Subject has the right to object at any time to the processing of

their personal data for the purpose in question, on grounds relating to their

personal situation.

Promotional activities for Services/Products similar to

those purchased

The Data Subject's personal data are processed in order to send

emails relating to promotions and offers relating to the Data

Controller's Services/Products identical and/or similar to those

covered by the current contract with the Data Subject, unless the

Data Subject objected to the processing, initially or during

subsequent communications.

The legal basis for the processing is the Data Controller's legitimate interest

in promoting products or services analogous which may reasonably be of

interest to the Data Subject, given the balance of the rights of the latter and

the Data Controller.

The Data Subject has the right to object at any time to the processing of

their personal data for the purpose in question, on grounds relating to their

personal situation.

Promotional activities for Services/Products offered by

Aruba

The Data Subject's personal data are processed in order to send,

with specific consent, promotional communications and offers

relating to the Data Controller's Services/Products through

traditional methods (e.g. ordinary mail, landline calls) and/or

automated methods (e.g. email, SMS, MMS, pre-recorded calls).

The legal basis of this processing is the consent initially granted by the Data

Subject for the processing itself, which may freely be withdrawn at any time,

without prejudice to the lawfulness of any previous processing.

If the Data Subject refuses to give their consent, it will not be possible to use

the relevant services, without this entailing detrimental consequences for

the contractual relationship with the Data Controller.

Promotional activities for Services/Products of the Aruba

Group companies

The Data Subject's personal data are processed in order to send,

with specific consent, communications of promotions and offers

of Services/Products of Aruba Group companies through

traditional methods (e.g. ordinary mail, landline calls) and/or

automated methods (e.g. email, SMS, MMS, pre-recorded

phone calls).

The legal basis of this processing is the consent initially granted by the Data

Subject for the processing itself, which may freely be withdrawn at any time,

without prejudice to the lawfulness of any previous processing.

If the Data Subject refuses to give their consent, it will not be possible to use

the relevant services, without this entailing detrimental consequences for

the contractual relationship with the Data Controller.

Profiling

The Data Subject's personal data are processed, with specific

consent, for profiling purposes such as the analysis of the

transmitted data and the purchased Services/Products in order

to offer advertising messages and/or business deals that are

aligned with user selections.

The legal basis of this processing is the consent initially granted by the Data

Subject for the processing itself, which may freely be withdrawn at any time,

without prejudice to the lawfulness of any previous processing.

If the Data Subject refuses to give their consent, it will not be possible to use

the relevant services, without this entailing detrimental consequences for

the contractual relationship with the Data Controller.

TO WHOM DO WE COMMUNICATE

THE DATA SUBJECT'S DATA

CATEGORIES OF RECIPIENT PURPOSE

Companies belonging to the Aruba

S.p.A. Group (“Aruba Group”)

Fulfilment of administrative and accounting requirements, as well as those connected with the

services requested

Privacy Policy

ARUBA

v.2.6\_ASOn_23.10.2023

3

Aruba S.p.A.

Via San Clemente No.53, Ponte San Pietro 24036 (BG)

VAT Reg. No. 01573850516 | Tax ID No. 04552920482

REA [Administrative and Economic Index] BG 434483 | Share Capital € 4,000,000 fully paid up | Certified email:

aruba@aruba.pec.it | Website aruba.it

Third party providers and companies

belonging to the Aruba Group

Performance of services (assistance, maintenance, delivery/shipping of products, performance of

additional services, providers of networks and electronic communication services) associated with

the requested service

Credit and electronic payment

institutions, banks/post offices

Managing deposits, payments, reimbursements associated with the contractual service

External professionals/consultants and

consulting firms

Fulfilment of legal requirements, exercising rights, protecting contractual rights, credit recovery

Financial Administration, Public

Agencies, Legal Authorities,

Supervisory and Oversight Authorities

Fulfilment of legal requirements, defence of rights; lists and registers held by Public Authorities or

similar agencies based on specific regulations relating to the requested service

Formally mandated subjects or those

with recognized legal rights

Legal representatives, administrators, guardians, etc.

Persons belonging to these categories operate independently as separate data controllers or as data processors appointed by the Data

Controller. The Data Controller's personnel that are specially authorised for processing, including interns, temporary workers, consultants, may

also have knowledge of the data, in relation to the performance of their assigned tasks. In no case shall personal data be disclosed and they

shall not, therefore, be accessible by undefined parties, in any form, for example by them being made available or subject to consultation.

HOW WE PROCESS THE DATA

SUBJECT'S DATA

The data shall be processed using manual, electronic and remote means and in accordance with the requirements set by the relevant

legislation, which seeks to ensure the confidentiality, integrity and availability of the Data, and to avoid material or moral damages.

WHERE WE PROCESS THE DATA

SUBJECT'S DATA

The Data Subject's data is stored in archives located in European Union countries. Where necessary for the pursuit of the stated purposes,

the Data Subject's Data may be transferred abroad, to countries/organizations outside the European Union guaranteeing a level of personal

data protection deemed adequate by the European Commission by its own decision or, otherwise, on the basis of other appropriate safeguards,

such as the Standard Contractual Clauses adopted by the European Commission or the Data Subject's consent. The Data Subject is entitled

to obtain a copy of any appropriate safeguards, as well as the list of countries/organizations to which the data has been transferred by writing

to privacy@staff.aruba.it.

HOW LONG WE RETAIN THE DATA

SUBJECT'S DATA

The Data are stored in a form which enables the Data Subject to be identified for no longer than is necessary for the collection purposes, given

the laws covering the activities and sectors in which the Data Controller operates.

The Data necessary to comply with tax and accounting obligations are retained for 10 years from the termination of the contract (art. 2220 of

the Civil Code).

The Data related to unpaid or canceled or unfinished order requests are retained for 3 months.

In case of Mail or Connectivity Services the internet traffic data are retained for 6 years.

Once the periods thus established have transpired, the Data will be deleted or processed anonymously, unless further retention is necessary

to comply with obligations or to comply with orders issued by Public Authorities and/or Supervisory Bodies.

WHAT ARE THE DATA

SUBJECT'S RIGHTS

The Data Subject shall contact privacy@staff.aruba.it to exercise the right to obtain, in the cases provided for in the Regulation, access to the

data concerning him/her, deletion of the data, correction of incorrect data, completion of incomplete data, limitation on processing the data,

portability of the data and opposition to the processing.

The Data Subject also has the right to lodge a claim with the competent Italian supervisory authority (Italian Personal Data Protection Authority)

or with the agency performing its duties and exercises its rights in the member State where the breach occurred, as provided for in Art. 77 of

the Regulation, as well as to file appropriate legal proceedings pursuant to Arts. 78 and 79 of the Regulation.

Privacy Policy

ARUBA

v.2.6\_ASOn_23.10.2023

4

Aruba S.p.A.

Via San Clemente No.53, Ponte San Pietro 24036 (BG)

VAT Reg. No. 01573850516 | Tax ID No. 04552920482

REA [Administrative and Economic Index] BG 434483 | Share Capital € 4,000,000 fully paid up | Certified email:

aruba@aruba.pec.it | Website aruba.it

Privacy Policy for Swite

In addition to the above, in the event of Swite Service the information required by law relating to the processing of personal data is provided

below. t should be noted that as part of any process of interaction with the so-called "social network(s)" previously chosen by the Data Subject

for importing of content via the Service(s), the Data Controller, on the basis of the settings and authorisations given independently by the Data

Subject to the social network chosen by him/her, will import various types of content present within the Data Subject’s account onto the

aforementioned social network. The client API uses the "social network" API services, for information purposes, the main information regarding

the "social network" services used for these functions is shown below:

SERVICE NAME REFERENCE INFORMATION INSTRUCTIONS ON HOW TO DISABLE FEATURES

YouTube API Services http://www.google.com/policies/privacy https://security.google.com/settings/security/permissions

Facebook Platform Graph API https://www.facebook.com/policy.php https://www.facebook.com/settings?tab=applications

Instagram Platform Graph API https://help.instagram.com/519522125107875 https://www.instagram.com/accounts/manage_access/

Twitter Developer Platform API https://twitter.com/privacy https://twitter.com/settings/applications

When registering or linking a social media site, the Data Subject accepts permissions that authorise the importing of certain types of content.

Depending on the social networks, the permissions provided, and the presence or absence of the data, Aruba imports the following categories

of data:

WHAT DATA

DO WE PROCESS?

CATEGORY OF DATA EXAMPLES OF TYPES OF DATA

Data linked to the account (Profile,

Page, Channel)

Account Name, Account Description, Avatar Photo, Cover Photo, Contact Information (Address,

Telephone, Email), Timetable

Data on individual content Photos, posts, tweets, videos, events, and/or reviews that the Customer has uploaded to social media

or shared on their feed (if the original author of the content allows the importing of data)

Metadata linked to individual content Title, description, link, thumbnail photo, upload date, rental tag, playlist or gallery to which it belongs

These data are used exclusively for creating and updating the Data Subject’s website. Permission can be directly withdrawn via the social media

platform by following the links in the table above. Revoking permissions blocks the importing of new content, but does not guarantee deletion of

all the data already imported. To delete data on Data Controller (and permission):

• For a single social media network, unlink that network from the "Social Media Connected" page

• For all social networks linked to a site, delete the site from the "Site Setup" page

• For all social media sites linked to an account, delete the account from the "Account Settings" page.

Privacy Policy for E-Security services / products

In addition to the above, in the event of “E-Security" Services/ Products, presented at www.pec.it, the information required by law relating to the

processing of personal data is provided below.

ABOUT

US

Joint Data Controllers Through its pro tempore legal representative, Aruba S.p.A., with registered office in Ponte San

Pietro (BG) at Via San Clemente No. 53

Through its pro tempore legal representative, Aruba PEC S.p.A., with registered office in Ponte San

Pietro (BG) at Via San Clemente No. 53

privacy@staff.aruba.it

Data Protection Officer (DPO) dpo@staff.aruba.it

Privacy Policy

ARUBA

v.2.6\_ASOn_23.10.2023

5

Aruba S.p.A.

Via San Clemente No.53, Ponte San Pietro 24036 (BG)

VAT Reg. No. 01573850516 | Tax ID No. 04552920482

REA [Administrative and Economic Index] BG 434483 | Share Capital € 4,000,000 fully paid up | Certified email:

aruba@aruba.pec.it | Website aruba.it

WHAT DATA

DO WE PROCESS?

CATEGORY OF DATA EXAMPLES OF TYPES OF DATA

Personal information In case of Digital Signature Service and/or qualified certificates: Data and registration documents of

the Service applicant, qualified certificate data and data contained in the qualified certificate, audit log

and certificate life cycle. Requests to issue certificates and documents provided by the applicants,

data contained in the qualified certificate, public keys provided by the applicants and personal

information of the applicants and holders (in the event of being different parties); results of checks

performed by the CA; Certificate suspension or revocation requests.

Log In case of Digital Signature Service and/or qualified certificates and/or Digital Preservation: Control

Journal (Audit Log), originating IP addresses associated with compilation of the remote form and the

logs on the associated transactions.

In case of Certified Email Service: Certified email messages log, Certified email messages log with

viruses.

Images and sounds In case of Digital Signature Service or Certified Email Service: Audio-video footage for remote visual

identification.

The processing of personal data contained in the audio-video footage for remote visual identification

for the Digital Signature Service is carried whit specific consent of the Data Subject, expressed prior

to the video recording.

Internet traffic Data In case of Certified Email Service: Data processed for the purpose of the conveyance of a

communication on an electronic communications network or for the billing thereof.

HOW LONG WE RETAIN THE DATA

SUBJECT'S DATA

In the case of Certification Authority Services (Digital signature, qualified certificates), Data and registration documents of the Service applicant,

the audio-video footage in case of remote visual identification, qualified certificate data and data contained in the qualified certificate, the data

from the audit log and the certificate life cycle are retained for 20 years from the termination of the contract.

In the case of a Qualified Electronic Time Validation Service, the logs (electronic registers) of the time validations issued are retained for 30

years unless a specific contractual agreement establishes a different duration, in any case always equal to or greater than the 20 years required

by law.

In case of Certified Email Service:

• The Data Subject’s personal data, any documents and audio-video footage for remote visual identification are retained for 10 years

from the termination of the contract.

• Internet traffic data are retained for 6 years.

• Certified email messages log and Certified email messages log with virus are retained for 30 months.

• The access data relating to the Certified Email Service by the holder are retained for 6 months.

• The personal data of the holder of the Certified Email Service mailbox and the name of the related mailbox are not subject to deletion

in accordance with the provisions of Agid.

Once the periods thus established have transpired, the Data will be deleted or processed anonymously, unless further retention is necessary to

comply with obligations or to comply with orders issued by Public Authorities and/or Supervisory Bodies.

Privacy Policy for SSL Server and Code Signing Certificates

In addition to the above, in the event of Services relating to the supply of SSL Server and Code Signing Certificates, the information required by

law relating to the processing of personal data is provided below.

ABOUT

US

Joint Data Controllers Through its pro tempore legal representative, Aruba S.p.A., with registered office in Ponte San Pietro

(BG) at Via San Clemente No. 53

Through its pro tempore legal representative, Actalis S.p.A., with registered office in Ponte San Pietro

(BG) at Via San Clemente No. 53

privacy@staff.aruba.it

Data Protection Officer (DPO) dpo@staff.aruba.it

Privacy Policy

ARUBA

v.2.6\_ASOn_23.10.2023

6

Aruba S.p.A.

Via San Clemente No.53, Ponte San Pietro 24036 (BG)

VAT Reg. No. 01573850516 | Tax ID No. 04552920482

REA [Administrative and Economic Index] BG 434483 | Share Capital € 4,000,000 fully paid up | Certified email:

aruba@aruba.pec.it | Website aruba.it

WHAT DATA

DO WE PROCESS?

CATEGORY OF DATA EXAMPLES OF TYPES OF DATA

Personal information Requests to issue certificates and documents provided by the applicants, data contained in the

qualified certificate, public keys provided by the applicants and personal information of the applicants

and holder (in the event of being different parties); results of checks performed by the CA; Certificate

suspension or revocation requests

Log Originating IP addresses associated with compilation of the remote form and the logs on the

associated transactions

HOW LONG WE RETAIN THE DATA

SUBJECT'S DATA

The applicant's registration data and documents, the certificate data, the data contained therein and the life cycle of the same are retained for

20 years from the termination of the contract.

Once the periods thus established have transpired, the Data will be deleted or processed anonymously, unless further retention is necessary to

comply with obligations or to comply with orders issued by Public Authorities and/or Supervisory Bodies.
